<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heeseok</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/</link><description>Recent content on Heeseok</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:31:54 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://skills.aiview.shop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Old</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/skills/old/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:18:40 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/skills/old/</guid><description>SKILLS
Segment 2D images Build 3D fonts Design 3D manipulator for the target application Repair 3D meshes enable 3D printing Compose boolean operations of 3D meshes in order to build a complex 3D object. Use the algorithms in ITK (Insignt Toolkit), VTK (Visualization Toolkit) software packages and port them Design hybrid volume-geometry rendering Reduce the dimensionality of large data sets using PCA (Principal Component Analysis) Register two-point clouds using ICP (Interative closest point) algorithm Interpolate 3D motion with polynomial equations over quaternions Interpolate spline curves and solve the related problem using their Frenet frame.</description></item><item><title>AI Visualization with CT</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/aiview-ct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:31:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/aiview-ct/</guid><description>Given a CSV file containing category names, (x, y) coordinates, and density values, generate a heatmap-based DICOM Image and DICOM Segmentation files for visualization in VolView.
Steps: Data Normalization: Normalize x, y coordinates to the range [0,1]. Normalize density values using the formula: df[&amp;ldquo;z&amp;rdquo;] = np.log1p(df[&amp;ldquo;z&amp;rdquo;] - zmin) / np.log1p(zmax - zmin) Category-wise Density Accumulation: Generate heatmaps for each category by applying Gaussian smoothing with sigma = 0.</description></item><item><title>Old</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/old/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:24:26 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/old/</guid><description>Experience
Build PRM (Product Road Map), TRM (Technology Road Map) Tailor Agile-Based Software Development Processes Create and maintain project documentations Build the checklist of software products and manage their quality Analyze competency of software development team members and evaluate it Build the development environment of PACS (picture archiving and communication system) Server/Client using Dcmtk Build the structure of directories and files to store DICOM (digital imaging and communications in medicine) and related files.</description></item><item><title>Old</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/portfolio/old/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 15:53:49 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/portfolio/old/</guid><description>WORK EXPERIENCE
2016.10 ~ Now, OSSTEM IMPLANT CO., LTD. Dental Implant Software Development Team Leader
Develop the software supporting digital guided implant planning surgery (a.k.a OneGuide SW) Design cooperation of PMS (patient management system) and OneGuide SW Design mini PACS system for OneGuide SW Evaluate and improve automatic registration algorithm with CT and Dental Scan Segment tooth regions from CT and generate a dental arch from them Place implant objects (implant, abutment, crown, etc.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 15:34:50 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/about/</guid><description>A results-oriented software solution architect with experience since 2005, specializing in analytical thinking and requirement-driven problem-solving. Proven ability to leverage technical expertise across various domains, particularly in medical software platform development (e.g., dental applications), medical device design software (e.g., dental implant guides and complex 3D models), and 3D visualization for AI-embedded environments.
Degree B.S., Computer Science, GPA 3.54/4.3, POSTECH, 1996.
M.S., Computer Engineering, GPA 4.15/4.3, POSTECH, 1998, Specialize Computer Graphics, &amp;ldquo;The intersection of two ruled surfaces&amp;rdquo; http://3map.</description></item></channel></rss>