<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heeseok</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/</link><description>Recent content on Heeseok</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 21:59:04 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://skills.aiview.shop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coordinate systems</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/skills/ct-coords/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 21:59:04 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/skills/ct-coords/</guid><description>Standard anatomical position of a human
World, anatomical and the image coordinate system in VolView</description></item><item><title>Old</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/skills/old/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:18:40 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/skills/old/</guid><description>Skills
Segment 2D images
Create 3D fonts
Design 3D manipulators for target applications
Repair 3D meshes to enable 3D printing
Perform boolean operations on 3D meshes to construct complex 3D objects
Utilize and port algorithms from ITK (Insight Toolkit) and VTK (Visualization Toolkit)
Design hybrid volume-geometry rendering systems
Apply PCA (Principal Component Analysis) to reduce the dimensionality of large datasets</description></item><item><title>Pbls 2024</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/portfolio/pbls-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 20:53:02 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/portfolio/pbls-2024/</guid><description>WORK EXPERIENCE
2023.04 ~ Now, Pebblous.
Project Achievements and Progress Summary
Until July 2024, I focused on developing the Supply Chain Planning (SCP) engine. I built and tested the LP/PP (Long-term Planning/Production Planning) integrated planning engine along with the testing environment. The SCP engine models the SCM (Supply Chain Management) system through surrogate modeling and utilizes AI to determine key policies based on the environment’s conditions. It handles order forecasting, corporate order allocation, order prioritization, and LP/PP policy decisions.</description></item><item><title>AI Visualization with CT</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/aiview-ct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:31:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/aiview-ct/</guid><description>Given a CSV file containing category names, (x, y) coordinates, and density values, generate a heatmap-based DICOM Image and DICOM Segmentation files for visualization in VolView.
Steps: Data Normalization: Normalize x, y coordinates to the range [0,1]. Normalize density values using the formula: df[&amp;ldquo;z&amp;rdquo;] = np.log1p(df[&amp;ldquo;z&amp;rdquo;] - zmin) / np.log1p(zmax - zmin) Category-wise Density Accumulation: Generate heatmaps for each category by applying Gaussian smoothing with sigma = 0.</description></item><item><title>Old</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/old/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:24:26 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/experience/old/</guid><description>Experience
Develop PRM (Product Roadmap) and TRM (Technology Roadmap)
Customize Agile-Based Software Development Processes
Create and maintain project documentation
Build and manage software product quality checklists
Analyze and evaluate software development team members' competencies
Set up PACS (Picture Archiving and Communication System) server/client development environments using DCMTK
Design directory and file structures for storing DICOM (Digital Imaging and Communications in Medicine) and related files</description></item><item><title>Old</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/portfolio/old/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 15:53:49 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/portfolio/old/</guid><description>WORK EXPERIENCE
2016.10 ~ 2022.12, OSSTEM IMPLANT CO., LTD. Dental Implant Software Development Team Leader
Develop the software supporting digital guided implant planning surgery (a.k.a OneGuide SW) Design cooperation of PMS (patient management system) and OneGuide SW Design mini PACS system for OneGuide SW Evaluate and improve automatic registration algorithm with CT and Dental Scan Segment tooth regions from CT and generate a dental arch from them Place implant objects (implant, abutment, crown, etc.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://skills.aiview.shop/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 15:34:50 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://skills.aiview.shop/about/</guid><description>A results-oriented software solution architect with experience since 2005, specializing in analytical thinking and requirement-driven problem-solving. Proven ability to leverage technical expertise across various domains, particularly in medical software platform development (e.g., dental applications), medical device design software (e.g., dental implant guides and complex 3D models), and 3D visualization for AI-embedded environments.
Degree B.S., Computer Science, GPA 3.54/4.3, POSTECH, 1996.
M.S., Computer Engineering, GPA 4.15/4.3, POSTECH, 1998, Specialize Computer Graphics, &amp;ldquo;The intersection of two ruled surfaces&amp;rdquo; http://3map.</description></item></channel></rss>